Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The castle was infiltrated by Longris, as well as others from the Golden Dawn who had been possessed by elves.
Yami and Finral were soon forced into a harrowing battle.
It doesn't matter how many of you there are, you'll never overpower us!
Keke! You're exactly the ones I want to slice on! So thanks for coming out!
With Jack's aid, they gained the upper hand.
After regrouping with Nozel and the others, the team entered the castle.
But Kevin had already invaded the Silva's home, where she attacked Solid and Nebra.
Noooo!
Nozel, it's you! And Noel!
Water creation magic! Sea dragon's roar!
Compass magic! Another Atlas!
Nozel and Noel joined the fray, but Kevin's compass magic took a toll.
Stop her, Nozel! Please!
Stay there, Solid. You'd only hold us back as you are now. I will handle this.
I will handle this.
T fellas
This one in the world
ṛṣṇa fighting
We've made a workshop
I can't do anything
It's time for everyone
It may be worse than anything
Quickly go down into peace
I'll become a new new year
t
yeah
via
Yeah!
La!
Don't win!
Mother!
Que ansurenne
Yay!
You could at least
try to fight back, little slowpoke!
That's odd, I thought
I trained you better than to start eating before I do!
If it makes you
If it makes you angry, then do something about it!
With a face like that? It must be hard to look in the mirror. You're lucky I'm always so kind to you.
That sad grimoire of yours is practically paper thin. Are you sure you're really royalty?
Not being able to control your own magic. That's the most pitiful thing I've ever heard.
And this wretch is my little sister? Embarrassing.
You will never be a member of my squad. There is no room in the Silver Eagles for a disgrace like you.
So sad.
Pitiful.
And would you believe the girl's been going outside alone every night so that she can practice her abilities on a dead tree?
The best part is, she always misses. Every once in a while a spell will backfire on her and she ends up soaked.
It's hilarious!
Really? I couldn't even do that as a joke! She's talented! Talented at being a failure, that is. I hate that she and I are related.
Noelle, I have decided which magic night squad you'll be joining.
You'll be a black bull. It's already been settled.
What?
Ah, the black bulls. The worst of them all. How very fitting.
They only do small missions in the sticks, don't they? Like hunting boars? Just your speed, Noelle.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. I went through all that training. I'll succeed. I can do it. I won't let you hurt my family anymore!
Let's show her our power, Noelle. The House Silva stands strong.
Great!
Unfortunately for you, this is a sealed space. Which means that no matter what you do, your attacks won't reach me.
Water creation magic! Sea Dragon's Lair!
You're just wasting magic and energy. What a shame. And I tried so hard to give you a peaceful death.
She's too good. What am I going to do? Even with mana skin, Sea Dragon's Lair won't have any effect in here.
Despite using all my strength, this is the best I can do.
All I can manage now are simple movements at close range. There's only one strategy.
You're quite determined. But I wonder how much longer you can keep this up.
He's struggling. Come on, think! If Oster or the other Black Bulls were here, I bet they could come up with some crazy idea!
Crazy idea!
Damn it! If we don't figure out something to counteract our magic, we'll have no way out!
No way out?
I may not be able to use creation magic in such a controlled environment.
But what if... I lose control?
Nozel! Lend me a hand!
This is... I don't understand!
You fool!
You just plotted a completely enclosed space with water!
Another Atlas can find everything within its fortress!
If I don't want to be drowned in my own spell, I have no choice but to call it off!
You wretched human!
No! I don't believe it! She annihilated me in a mere instant!
Amazing! It makes sense from Nozel, but not from her.
Um, guess we pulled it off, huh, Nozel?
Hey, I really appreciate you going along with my idea, even though it was a bit of a shot in the dark and all.
It was certainly unorthodox. Fighting that way is unbefitting of royalty.
But it still resulted in a victory for us.
You've learned many impressive things since you joined that squad.
I had feared, because you looked so much like our late mother, that I might lose her a second time.
I didn't expect you would ever become a strong person, so I decided that I had to protect you at any cost.
I tried to keep you from the battlefield.
But you proved me wrong, Noel. You're more capable now than I ever could have predicted you'd be.
What I mean is...
I... I apologize, Noel.
Nozel apologized?
That's impossible!
Thank you, Nozel.
Nozel?
We aren't out of danger yet.
We'd better see to Nebra's wounds.
What?
Nozel!
How did this happen? Please wake up!
I almost feel bad for you.
You're trapped now. Here. In this place.
There's no stopping it anymore. It's far too vast and powerful.
You're lying! There has to be some way to escape from this madness!
All you can do now is accept your fate. This is the price you'll pay for your sins, royals.
I won't give up. There's a solution to this. I know there is!
Think hard, Noel. You can defeat her!
You finally proved yourself to your brother, right? So you can do anything!
If you don't, Nozel and Nebra won't make it!
I would prefer to watch as you gradually give in to death.
But I think I'll have mercy on you sinful human fools and get this over with quickly instead.
They've been cruel to me. But still, I won't let her take away my family!
Long-range spells are out. Magic manipulation, too.
I need something simple that packs a punch. Something that doesn't need to travel far.
This is a spell I can only use because of where I am and who I am in this exact moment!
In order to manifest a magic ability, the most crucial component is the user's natural talent.
However, unwavering effort and training may also play a part.
In rare cases, a deeply heartfelt wish can grant power during a time of crisis.
Many royal mages are able to acquire spells intuitively by employing their innate prowess and natural resourcefulness.
Because of their advantage, those individuals rarely undergo training, do research, or have their lives endangered on the battlefield.
Although Noelle possessed considerable magic power and talent, she also worked hard to improve herself and risked her life in combat many times alongside the Black Bulls.
Her long suffering, combined with her resolute desire to protect her siblings, gave her all the power she needed to overcome her current challenge.
Noelle!
What kind of magic is that?
She's giving off an enormous amount of power.
That won't be enough, royal!
Royal?
Noelle!
How does she move so swiftly?
Is she riding the mana for my attacks and the disturbance they're creating in this sealed space like waves on the sea?
See? That armor must be a spell that lets her control nearby mana.
Fine. But can you avoid all of these?
I still have the advantage here.
If I can find the slightest hole in your defense, this world I've created will rip your armor clean off!
Just moments ago, I was struggling.
But now it feels like I've burst out of my cage.
I had no idea magic could make me feel so free.
I wonder if this is the same feeling my mother had.
Mother, the dancing princess of the battlefield.
How? How did you cut through everything I threw at you?
It's over!
We'll build compass!
These monocurrents you seem to dance through so elegantly.
I'm about to redirect them and send you straight to hell!
Okay.
You're mine now, royal brat!
Did she overrule my mana compulsion?
I'm not concerned with elegance.
This armor, anything that comes into contact with this mana, is under my control!
I'm fighting with everything I've got so I can move forward!
I'll crush you and this world you've made!
I'll crush you and this leverage!
Wاخ numbs engulfed!
Did I win?
Come on, let's get Nozell and Nebra to safety!
Oh no, I don't have enough magic left to fight these guys.
How dare you hurt Kiben? It appears we might have underestimated your strength, humans.
But that will not happen again. Be gone!
Solid behind you!
See? Now that's how you do a surprise attack.
Not bad, huh? Even better when you double it.
What kind of magic was that?
I've never seen anything like it.
Damned, humans. Stay on guard.
That last battle was flashy to say the least. So I kinda assumed it was gonna draw a crowd.
Sora!
Hey kid, don't you work for these people? Make yourself useful.
What's the matter with you dragging me into something this dangerous?
I'm the guy who saved your ass, remember? So you had better listen to me.
I can't!
You can and you will. Now hop to it, kid, or you won't have masters anymore.
Hey, it's Lord Nozell and Lady Nebra! They need my help! Bubble recovery magic! Bubble refresher!
Lord Solid, please bring Lord Nozell over here!
Lord Solid!
What's wrong? Are you taking a nap? Some royal magic knight you are, buddy.
How could you let this chick beat all three of you?
Maybe if you snobs didn't run your mouse off all the time, you would fight better!
I mean, this moron here is a captain, and he couldn't even look out for his own family!
Nozell.
You're finally getting your grimoire next year. I'm looking forward to finding out what sorts of
amazing things you're going to do.
I'll learn spells of unparalleled power, so that I can become a strong magic knight captain just like
you are, mother.
That's great. Solid and Nebra both have water magic like your father does.
And I have a feeling it might be the same for the little one, too.
The only one of my children who inherited my steel attribute was you, dear,
so be sure that you use it to protect your siblings, okay?
That's right. I should.
Royals like you are supposed to be more powerful than us commoners, right?
Come on, show a little spirit!
I think we've heard quite enough out of you-
Stop!
You- But Nozell, I don't-
Everything he's saying is true. If I let this be the end of me,
I'd be a disgrace. To the Royal House of Silva and the Silver Eagles.
I'll reinforce my body with magic.
He can fortify himself with mercury magic? What an advanced technique!
Are you ready, Noelle?
Yeah.
You snooty rich kids have so much magic power, it makes me sick. Tone it down some for the rest of us,
would you? Ash magic! Revelation of the Cowardly!
Now! Take my magic with you, Noelle!
I've got you!
Not quite.
She's too fast.
We'll catch her!
It's trap magic.
And there's more where that came from. The revelation of the Cowardly shows where I've placed
each of my trap spells. The second they screw up, these royals will be all over them.
In that condition, you won't be able to avoid this!
Noelle!
He's not fazed at all by the strength of our spell.
What kind of magic was that?
Bunch of amateurs. Guess you don't know about complicated techniques like my counter traps.
Water creation magic! Sea dragon's roar!
It looks like your control is starting to falter, little girl.
Mercury magic. Rain of silver!
That's nothing to me!
These spells have been evolving for years. It's complex human magic.
But you elves wouldn't know about that either, would you?
You elf.
人生は全長だ
そう感じることもある
自分らしくとは何も反対とはない
愛なんて知らない 笑うのも痛い
でも本当は強くないよ
歩くべき道をずっと手探りだけで探してる
取り付けたらを止める
永世君の寂 lain
NOマター WHAT думаете
私と僕は永遠と会う
Koreaとして誰が如何 никаких
永世君の寂 fluid
僕は永遠と本当の兄弟
私たちの好きな兄弟
アラーについて
vistoに109 翌日
公他の寂 jury
魔女王
我当然やる
そこにも
俺は誰を嘗まり
You